

Maciej Szostak Frontend developer

Contact

Phone number

+48 506 783 448

E-mai

maciek.szostak55@gmail.com

GitHub

github.com/MSzostaq

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mszostaq/

Location

Cracow, Poland

Languages

- Polish (native)
- English (B2)

Soft skills

- Communicative
- Creative
- Open-minded
- Organised
- Reliable

About me

I'm a front-end developer with nearly 4 years of handson experience in crafting exceptional web solutions. I'm passionate about writing, creating clean and efficient code that results in stunning, user-friendly experiences.

Tech stack

- TypeScript / JavaScript
- React / NextIS
- Redux / Redux Saga / Redux Toolkit
- CSS3 / SASS / TailwindCSS / CSS in JS
- Jest / Cypress
- RESTful APIs / GraphQL

- git
- Postman
- Vercel
- lira
- basics of Adobe Illustrator
- basics of Adobe Photoshop

Work history

Frontend developer at BrandBuddies 🔗

ReasonApps, Cracow 01/2023 - current

- Marketing platform which allows influencers to find and apply to campaigns designed by well known brands.
- Project built from scratch using NextJS, using server-side rendering to improve SEO and performance.
- Communication with RESTful API.
- Styles developed using TailwindCSS and SASS.
- E2E tests developed using Cypress.

Frontend developer at Fansi 🔗

ReasonApps, Cracow

02/2022 - current

- Ecommerce platform, consisting of admins' and influencers' panel which allows influencers to connect and advertise their products on the marketplace.
- Maintaining project written in NextJS while improving SEO and performance.
- Communication with GraphQL API.
- Styles developed using TailwindCSS and SASS.

Education

Cracow University of TechnologyBachelor of Engineering

10/2018 - 01/2022

Transport, Engineering studies

My graduate work was about technologies used in rail transport to communicate with passengers

AGH University of Science and Technology

Postgraduate studies

10/2023 - 06/2024

Software Development Methods

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).